<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipes</string>
    <string name="Recipes">Recipes</string>
    <string name="Language">EN</string>
    <string name="Breakfast">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="Lunch">Lunch</string>
    <string name="Dinner">Dinner</string>
    <string name="Russian">Русский</string>
    <string name="English">English</string>
    <string name="Chinese">中文</string>
    <string name="language_select">Select a language</string>
    <string name="back_btn">Back</string>
    <string name="Recipe_1">Cheesecakes</string>
    <string name="Recipe_3">Fried rice</string>
    <string name="Ingredients">Ingredients:</string>
    <string name="Recipe_2">Meat with cherries</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_1">1) Cottage cheese 400 gr \n2) Eggs 1 pc. \n3) Sugar 2 table.l.\n4) Salt (pinch) to taste\n5) Vanilla sugar 5 g \n6) Wheat flour (plus for the subfoil) 40 g \n7) Vegetable oil 2 tablespoons.</string>
    <string name="Cooking">Step-by-step cooking:</string>
    <string name="Cooking_1">STEP 1: Measure out the necessary ingredients. Cottage cheese is suitable for any fat content. Vanilla sugar can be replaced with vanillin. \nSTEP 2: If the cottage cheese is coarse or flaky, pass it through a blender to get a homogeneous structure. \nSTEP 3: Put the cottage cheese in a suitable sized bowl. Add salt, sugar, vanilla sugar, and mix. Take the amount of sugar to taste. \nSTEP 4: Add the beaten egg to the cottage cheese, mix well. \nSTEP 5: Pour the flour through a sieve, mix thoroughly. \nSTEP 6: Leave the curd dough on the table for 15 minutes. \nSTEP 7: Sprinkle the table with a little flour, roll the sausage out of the dough. Divide the dough into equal parts depending on the desired size of the cheesecakes. \nSTEP 8: Roll each part of the dough into a bun, then press down to make a round, medium-thick cheese cake. \nSTEP 9: Heat the vegetable oil in a frying pan, put the cheesecakes. Fry the cheesecakes over moderate heat until golden brown. \nSTEP 10: When the cheesecakes are browned, turn them over to the other side and fry until cooked over low heat.</string>
    <string name="timer_btn_text_1">Frying cheesecakes</string>
    <string name="stop_btn">STOP</string>
    <string name="Ready_toast">Done!</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_2">1) Beef 400 g \n2) Cherry 300 g \n3) Thyme, thyme (3-5 sprigs) 10 g\n4) Ground black pepper to taste \n5) Salt to taste</string>
    <string name="Cooking_2">STEP 1: Prepare the necessary ingredients. I have a beef tenderloin, you can take any meat from any part of the carcass, as long as it is boneless. My cherries are fresh, but frozen and canned will do here - just drain the excess juice from them. \nSTEP 2: Wash the meat well, dry it and cut it into small pieces. \nSTEP 3: Put the beef in a bowl, add salt, pepper, and mix. Leave to marinate for 20 minutes at room temperature.\nSTEP 4: Wash the cherries, if they are fresh, dry them, remove the seeds. Drain all the juice from the canned one and leave it in a colander for 5 minutes. Defrost the frozen one, remove excess liquid. Get rid of the bones. \nSTEP 5: Put the meat and cherries together with the meat juice in a suitable baking dish. You can put everything mixed up, or you can put it in layers. I did it mixed up. \nSTEP 6: Arrange the thyme sprigs on top. STEP 7: Bake the meat with cherries in a preheated 180 °C oven for about 1 hour. Determine the exact baking time by your oven - it may take you more or less than me. To prevent the meat from being tough, you can periodically pour juice from the bottom of the mold.</string>
    <string name="timer_btn_text_2">Marinating meat</string>
    <string name="timer_btn_text_3">Baking in the oven</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_3">1) Rice. 1 stack. \n2) Water 2 stacks. \n3) Onion 1 pc. \n4) Vegetable oil 30 g \n5) Salt to taste \n6) Spices are dry to taste</string>
    <string name="Cooking_3">STEP 1: Prepare the ingredients. Peel the onion and rinse it in cold water. Using a sharp knife, chop the onion finely.\nSTEP 2: Pour a little vegetable oil into a hot frying pan and put the chopped onion. Fry the onion until golden brown. Stir occasionally to avoid burning.\nSTEP 3: While the onion is frying, prepare the required amount of rice. Rinse it several times in cold water. Then drain all the water using a colander.\nSTEP 4: When the onion is fried, add the washed rice to it in the pan. Stir and fry everything together for 3-4 minutes.\nSTEP 5: Add some salt and spices to the rice. To give the rice a beautiful yellow color, you can add a little turmeric. Mix everything well.\nSTEP 6: Pour the required amount of hot water into the pan. Stir and bring to a boil. Then cover the pan with a lid, make a minimum heat and leave to cook for about 10-15 minutes. We need the cereal to absorb the liquid.\nSTEP 7: As soon as the water is absorbed into the rice, turn off the heat and leave the rice to stand under the lid for another 15 minutes. Then you can serve it hot.</string>
    <string name="timer_btn_text_4">Roasting rice with onions</string>
    <string name="timer_btn_text_5">Stewing rice</string>
</resources>